https://www.diamondpeak.com/privacy-policy

The MountainThe MountainMain Menu Tahoe Views & Mountain Cams Hours of Operation Village Terrain Park Conditions Trail Map Snowmaking & Grooming Sustainability & Environmental Efforts Virtual Tour Mountain Safety & Policies Frequently Asked Questions Food and Beverage Reviews Uphill Use Policy Steeps & Stashes Tickets & PassesTickets & PassesMain Menu Season Passes & Perks Lift Tickets Specials Group Tickets & Special Events Diamond Peak Gift Cards Lessons & RentalsLessons & RentalsMain Menu Child Ski Center Ski & Ride Center Equipment Rentals Beginners Tips for Kids Lake Tahoe Kids Ski/Snowboard Lesson Series Lesson Cancellation and Refund Policy Plan A VisitPlan A VisitMain Menu COVID FAQ: Know Before You Go Why Families Love Diamond Peak Getting Here Ski Shuttle Visit Incline Village Ski and Stay Lodging AboutAboutMain Menu Contact Us Employment Facts & Figures Diamond Peak History Master Plan Update Process Master Plan FAQ News & EventsNews & EventsMain Menu Events News Social Hub Pic of the Day Sign Up for Alerts Explore Incline Explore InclineMain MenuGolf InclineMeetings & WeddingsParks & RecCommunity
Search
Contact Directions Tickets
Golf InclineMeetings & WeddingsParks & RecCommunity
Diamond Peak
Home>Privacy StatementPrivacy Statement
The following information applies to all Incline Village General Improvement District (IVGID) provided websites, ecommerce sites, and IVGID affiliated pages, sites and social media that may be provided through third-parties, including, but not limited to, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, Vimeo, etc. Your privacy is very important to us. IVGID is committed to protecting that privacy and will never share nor sell your personal information and/or email address to a third-party unless we are legally required to do so, with the exception of government agency partners (i.e., Washoe County). IVGID may use personal and information to better communicate to you regarding updates, deals and related news. In all email correspondence of this nature, IVGID will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such communications. This will allow you to remove yourself from any IVGID email list at any time.All information that may be collected, submitted, and/or posted becomes public record that may be subject to request, inspection and copying by the public, unless an exemption in the law exists.  For instance, if personal information is requested or volunteered, District policy, Nevada rules and regulations or the Federal Privacy Act of 1974 may protect it from disclosure. Board of Trustee correspondence submitted by email will be considered and treated as public information.  Additionally, communications collected, submitted, and or/posted are not private communications, including personal information you may provide, therefore others may read your communications without your knowledge.  You should always use caution when providing any personal information about yourself or your children.The District does not control or endorse the content, messages or information that may be collected, submitted, and/or posted and specifically disclaims any liability with regard to same and any actions resulting from your participation.The District uses cookies to personalize content and ads, to understand how you interact with our website, to provide social media features and to analyze our website traffic. We may share information about your use of our website with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. If you continue to use this website, you agree to receive all cookies and agree to our use of cookies. If you do not agree to our use of cookies, please discontinue use of our website.
Snow Report
Mountain Cams Pic of the Day Search Get DirectionsSpecial AnnouncementsCOVID FAQ - Know Before You GoSeason Pass PerksKids 6 & Under Ski FREEReviews & TestimonialsSTOKE Certification & Sustainability EffortsPurchase Season Passes Online...While Supplies Last!Still Hiring for Winter JobsQuestions? Reach us775-832-1177info@diamondpeak.com
